hello
my name is dr sabot pandit
and it's nice to meet you all
have you ever asked big questions
i mean big questions like
does god really exist
of course you have
everyone has asked this question at some
time or the other
some quickly push it out of their minds
some struggle for a little while to
answer it and then when it gets all
sticky they just give up
others are convinced that it can never
ever be answered
but
what if there is a reasonable approach
to the question
and what if it leads to a reasonable
conclusion that satisfies the mind
by satisfaction
i don't mean absolute proof
there is no such thing on earth you know
why
because belief
finally
is a very personal and private choice
that you and i are morally free to make
so when i use the words mentally
satisfying i am talking about a
conclusion that is so reasonable
that even if you choose to not believe
it
you cannot provide a logical
counter-argument to it you cannot
intellectually refute the evidence
now
what if it is possible
what if it is within our reach would you
be interested really really interested
if you are
then come
we will look at this together in an
honest and open manner
no tricky explanations with hidden
agendas trying to hook the people and
pull them to one side
and on the other hand no stubbornly
holding to a position no matter what
even though the evidence does not
support it but actually points to the
other side
in other words
we make a conscious choice
to go where the evidence leads
like plateau the greek thinker
he quoted socrates and said
go where the argument leads
sounds good
impressive
it is also a caution don't pull the
argument where you want it to go so our
aim is to be pulled by the evidence to
the truth of the matter
so the two big fundamental questions are
does god really exist and number two
can we identify this god with any degree
of confidence
what do you think
listen
after talking with smart people all over
the world for years
i am convinced that we can tackle these
questions with good reliable information
placed in a logical sequence so you and
i can see and follow the steps of
reasoning
and when that is done
we can reach an intellectually sound and
satisfying conclusion
so i invite you
if you feel inclined
whether believers skeptic atheist or
agnostic let's do it together
of course it will challenge you and it
will make you think
but it will also be very enjoyable in
fact i promise there's plenty of
information just waiting for you so come
come search with me
every presentation
will be followed by a q a session
come with your questions
no matter how simple or complex they are
see you at the
meeting have a great day